中城公民报
闪电侠失踪  消失于危机之中
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
我们看着那报纸头版已经有四年了
We've been looking at that front page for four years.
由爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦撰写
2024年4月25日星期四
我就是写那篇文章的人  巴里
I'm the one that writes that article, Barry.
我老板的丈夫是闪电侠
My boss' husband is the Flash?
大家什么都不告诉我
Oh, God, nobody tells me anything.
这种物质会治愈
This substance appears to heal
人体中所有的弱点
any and all weaknesses in the human body.
我已经能学会了掌控它
I've learned to control it.
这将是我最后的杰作
This is my final masterpiece:
永生
life eternal.
我已经见识过你那种生活了
I've seen your version of life.
简直就是噩梦
It's a nightmare.
-我想给你看这个  -我见过那个胸针
- I want to show you this. - I recognize that pin.
我有个后续问题
I have a follow-up question.
闪 电 侠
第六季
第七集
翻得真带劲
Whoo! That was quite the tumble.
我猜你正纳闷我为什么要这样对你
I guess you're wondering why I'm doing this to you.
你是邪恶的  我懂
You're evil. I get it.
我打赌你有好一阵子感觉不到自己会死
I bet it's been a while since you felt your own mortality,
而我的能力  和你的一样
but my powers, like yours,
作用于分子层面
work on a cellular level.
让我为你展示一番
Allow me to demonstrate.
当我把你送去铁山监狱的时候
You know, Iron Heights... is gonna send me
我将会收到一份感谢果篮
a thank-you basket when I drop you off as a gift.
我已经给予了你一份礼物
I've already given you a gift,
现在我要将它拿回来
and now I'm gonna need it back.
我的使命是治愈全人类
My destiny is to heal all of mankind.
你和你的朋友不能阻止这一切
You and your friends can't be allowed to prevent that.
生命的延续需要你的死亡
Life demands your death.
拉尔夫
Ralph!
拉尔夫  拉尔夫
Ralph... Ralph.
拉尔夫  坚持住
Ralph, come on.
-帮我们一把  -发生什么事了
- Give us a hand. - What happened?
拉姆齐干的
Ramsey.
坚持住  导师  我们还要
Come on, Coach, we-- we still gotta go
还要去公路旅行呢  对吗
on that road trip, right?
他要死了
He's gonna die.
-冰霜  我们怎么救他  -我不知道
- Frost, how do we save him? - I don't know!
我挽救不了这种情况
I can't fix this.
也许凯特琳可以
Uh, maybe Caitlin can.
拉尔夫的弹性细胞不能像以往一样自我修复了
Ralph's elastic cells aren't mending like they used to.
拉姆齐肯定变得更强了
Ramsey must be getting stronger.
-拉尔夫不能自我治愈了吗  -不能
- So Ralph can't heal himself? - No.
-但也许你可以  -什么
- But maybe you can. - What?
你的极速治愈  是我们所见过的事物里
Your speed healing is the only thing we've seen
唯一能够修复如此严重损害的能力
that can repair damage this severe.
也许给他输你的血可以治好他
Maybe if we gave him a blood transfusion, that would fix him.
你是什么意思
What are you saying?
我可以把极速治愈的能力给拉尔夫
I--I--I could give Ralph my speed healing?
理论上  暂时地  是可以的
Theoretically, temporarily, yes.
我不知道  这是我们没接触过的领域
I don't know, we're sort of in uncharted medical territory here.
但你的血型是O型阴性
But your blood type is O-negative,
你是万能献血者
so you're a universal donor.
各位  拉尔夫是有弹性的
Guys, Ralph is elastic.
针头无法刺穿他的皮肤
No needle can puncture through his skin.
我可以穿越他
I can phase him.
那样有会用吗
Will that work?
动手吧
Do it.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
他怎么样了
Hey. How is he?
多亏了你  他情况稳定了
He's stable thanks to you.
我们联系了天眼会  他们会将拉尔夫
We contacted A.R.G.U.S., and they're gonna move Ralph
转移到一个安全的医疗机构进行恢复
to a secure medical facility for recovery.
西斯科和凯特琳在为他的转移做准备
Cisco and Caitlin are prepping for transport right now.
别担心  好吗  他会好起来的
Hey, don't worry, okay? He's gonna pull through.
不是因为那个
It's not that.
如果我不在这里会怎样
What if I hadn't been here?
相比于即将到来的危机
Ralph's fight was nothing
拉尔夫和拉姆齐这场架根本不算什么
compared to what's coming.
危机还有两天就要发生了
Crisis is only two days away.
我们都准备好了  我保证
And we're all ready, I promise.
爱瑞丝  我还没为团队准备好
Iris, if I haven't prepared the team--
你已经为我们准备好了  巴里
You have prepared us, Barry.
不要因为拉尔夫的遭遇让你满心怀疑
Hey, don't let what happened to Ralph fill you with doubt.
你已经做了该做的  我们都准备好了
You've done the work. We're ready...
无论接下来会发生什么
For whatever comes next...
我准备给你个机会去自首
I'm gonna give you one chance to turn yourself in.
说实话  我希望你不会去
Honestly, I hope you don't take it.
没必要惊动警察
Well, there's no need to involve the authorities.
我只想和你聊聊
I just want to talk...
闪电侠
Flash.
当然了  你就是闪电侠
Of course. You're the Flash.
但怎么会  是什么时候的事
But how did-- when?
你被闪电击中
You were struck by lightning.
故事的起因是这样
That is quite the origin story.
我不知道你是怎么做到的
I don't know how you're doing this.
不管你是否真实存在  我都会找到你
Real or not, I'm coming for you.
然而我不是你最关心的问题吧
And yet I'm not your foremost concern, am I?
你更关心的是你将死于即将到来的
Not as much as your inevitable demise in a coming...
危机吧
crisis?
天哪  你还真是充满惊喜啊
Goodness, you really are full of surprises, aren't you?
那么告诉我  当你看到这些排列时
So tell me, when you saw all those permutations,
数十亿可能的未来都以你的死亡而告终
billions of possible futures all ending in your death...
我在当中扮演了什么角色
What role did I play?
你没有
You didn't.
你不在场
You weren't there.
真的吗  一个都没有吗
Really? Not even in one?
那还是那句话
Then again,
你从没想预料到吧
you never saw this coming did you?
说实话  我也没预料到
Frankly, neither did I.
只有经历过才会相信不可能之事  对吧
Makes one believe in the impossible, doesn't it?
你好像很害怕  你应该害怕
You look scared. You should be.
毕竟  那是世界末日对吧
After all, it is the end of the world, isn't it?
我的天
Oh, my--
什么  闪电侠
What's that, Flash?
巴里·艾伦
中城警局勋章
你认为我应该揭发我的老板
You think I should bust my boss
又瞒了我一个秘密吗
for keeping yet another secret from me?
我也这么认为
Yeah, me too.
中城公民报
闪电侠消失于危机中
2019年12月11日
放下你手中的活  《公民报》有新报道
Drop what you're doing. "The Citizen" has a new story.
看看这个
Look at these.
你是从哪拍到这些照片的
Where did you get these photos?
用领结相机拍到的
I pulled them from a bow tie camera.
说来话长  重点是
Long story. Look, the point is,
就是这个人绑架了你表姐伊丝丽兰萨
this is the same guy that kidnapped your cousin Esperanza
并且强行把她变成超能力刺客
and turned her into a meta-assassin against her will.
其中一张照片  这一张
One of these photos, this one,
拍到我们的神秘人从车里出来
shows our mystery man getting out of his car.
我爸查过他的车牌
My dad traced his plates
并查到这辆车在附近租了一个停车位
and tracked the car to a rented parking space at a nearby lot.
现在我们只要等他出现就行了
So now all we have to do is to wait for him to show up.
好极了  我想问问
Cool. Just checking,
你还有其他的报道要先写吗
are there any other stories you wanna work on first?
还有什么比这更值得我们关注的
What could need our attention more than this?
你表姐是受害者  阿莱格拉
Your cousin was a victim, Allegra,
而某个秘密组织在利用她
and now some secret organization is using her.
还有多少人受他们利用
I mean, how many others are they using?
我们要帮助他们
We need to help them.
是的  没人比我
Right, I mean, no one wants to find out
更想查出伊丝丽兰萨发生了什么事  但是
what happened to Esperanza more than me, but...
这真的是你现在最关心的事吗
is this really what matters the most to you right now?
是的  快点去拿你的东西
Yeah. Now come on, get your stuff.
卡米拉会看看她是否能修复其他的照片
Kamilla is going to see if she can recover any other photos.
我和你要去盯梢
You and I have a stakeout date.
你说了算
You're the boss.
大脑活动一切正常
Brain activity looks good.
没迹象显示你会疯
No sign that you're going nuts.
我的血液没问题吗
And my blood work?
全血细胞计数  代谢率
CBC, metabolic rate,
全都符合正常的极速者
all normal for a speedster,
只是皮质醇有一点点高
just a small spike in cortisol.
凯蒂说她手腕上的睡眠监测器
Katie says that sleep monitor on your wrist
会告诉我们是否有严重的问题
will tell us if there's anything seriously wrong,
但如果你要问我  你只是做了一场噩梦
but if you ask me, you just had a nightmare.
我不知道
I don't know.
拉姆齐看起来很真实
Ramsey seemed so real.
事情有些不对劲
Something feels off.
我只是想不出哪里不对
I just can't put my finger on it.
你好
Hi, there.
我是《公民报》的爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦
My name is Iris West-Allen. I'm with "The Citizen."
我可不可以问你几个问题
I was wondering if I could ask you a few questions.
抱歉  没兴趣
Sorry, not interested.
同一家报社  同样的问题
Hi. Same paper, same question.
到底是要干什么
What the hell's going on here?
我没时间和你们说  我上班要迟到了
I don't have time for this. I'm late for work.
要去哪里上班呢
Which is where, exactly?
不关你们的事
None of your business.
你说得对
Okay, you know what? You're right.
我们只好刊登没有任何评论的照片了
We will just run our photos without any comments.
什么照片
What photos?
你知道吗  我相信你的老板
You know what? I'm sure your employer
会很喜欢这免费宣传的
will love the free exposure.
好吧  就照你的来
All right, have it your way.
别动  我有点击枪
Easy, I've got a Taser.
而我有张明信片
And I have a business card.
漩涡快递
响誉高端运输
Maelstrom Couriers,
the premiere name in high-end transport.
具体运输些什么
Transporting what exactly?
任何有钱人想要秘密运送的东西
Whatever the wealthy would prefer to keep under the radar,
一般都是专业物品
specialty items mostly.
那个昏迷的女人是政府指派的工作
That woman in a coma was a government job.
迈斯特的派对  更确切地说是给
Meister's party, well, that was more like designated driving
旧瘾复发的亿万富翁当指定司机
for billionaires falling off the wagon.
今天是无价的家族珠宝
Today it's priceless family jewels.
你是给超级有钱人做专车司机的
You're an Uber for the uberrich.
我现在是要迟到了
What I am is late.
抱歉打扰你了  谢谢你
Sorry to bother you. Thank you.
-这是条死路  -没错
- That was a bust. - Yep.
好的一面是  我们有时间做别的
But the bright side is, we have time for other stories
可能被忽视的故事  有什么想法吗
we might be putting off. Got any in mind?
我不知道
You know, I don't know,
我觉得我们漏掉了什么
I think there's something that we missed.
我还不想放弃这个
I don't want to move off of this yet.
妈妈
Mom?
这又是一场噩梦吗
Is this another nightmare?
不  巴里  这个要糟糕得多
No, Barry. This is much, much worse.
你是神速力
You're the Speed Force.
是的
Yes.
我们已经很久没这样子谈过话了
It's been a while since we've talked like this.
我很想念
I've missed it.
你需要帮助
You need to help.
我不明白我是怎么了
I don't understand what's happening to me.
你用你的血救了你朋友的命
You used your blood to save your friend's life,
但与此同时  你威胁到了自己的生命
but in the process, you've endangered your own.
拉姆齐袭击时的一小部分细胞还存在
A small amount of Ramsey's cells remain from the attack,
肉眼无法看到
hidden from the eye.
拉姆齐感染了我
Ramsey's infected me.
比你想的更严重  拉姆齐的意识
And more than you realize. Ramsey's sentience,
他存在的基本  就储存在他的细胞中
his very being, resides in his cells.
所以他才知道我是闪电侠
That's how he knew I'm the Flash,
还有危机
about Crisis.
如果这都是我脑袋里发生的
If this-if this is all in my mind,
那我真正的身体呢
then where's my real body?
在你的朋友  冰霜检查你之后
After your friend, Frost, examined you,
你回到家  把钥匙放到了那盘子里
you came back home, dropped your keys in that bowl,
倒了一杯水
poured a glass of water,
然后感染就占据了主权
then the infection took hold.
我们说话这时  拉姆齐的感染正在扩张
As we speak, Ramsey's infection is spreading
遍布了你的身体和思想
through your body and your mind.
你的极速治疗正在与他的传染对抗
Your speed-healing is trying to hold off his disease,
但最终
but, ultimately,
只有你能抵抗住他
it's up to you to resist him.
他想要杀死我吗
Is he trying to kill me?
恐怕更糟
Worse, I'm afraid.
他想要控制你
He wants to take control of you
让你听令于他
and bend you to his will.
那他一定会失败
Then he's gonna lose.
肯定有什么能告诉我们
There must be something that points
伊丝丽兰萨在哪里被带走的
to where Esperanza was taken.
我不知道  医院记录吗
I don't know. Hospital records?
或是那个拍卖的照片呢
Or what about that auction photo?
那个神秘人是条死胡同  但巴里说过
That mystery man was a dead end, but Barry did say
那个宴会上有很多阴暗的人
that there were a lot of shady people at that gala,
所以我不知道  也许他们其中一个是线索
so, I don't know, maybe one of them might be a new lead.
或者
Or...
我们可以谈谈你丈夫是闪电侠的事
we could talk about how your husband is the Flash.
你是怎么
How did you--
-纳什·威尔斯告诉我的  -你不会是要
- Nash Wells told me. - You're not gonna--
这就是你一直想要和我说的事吗
Is this the story that you've been trying to tell?
阿莱格拉  巴里的身份不能曝光
Allegra, Barry's identity cannot be exposed.
不  不是那个
No, not that.
中城公民报
是这个
This.
闪电侠消失于危机中
你已经逃避它一整天了
You've been avoiding it all day.
这个还不到发布的时候
It's not time for that yet.
根据这上边说的  会在两天后发布
Well, according to this, it will be in two days,
你可以说是直觉  但我觉得
and call it a hunch, but I don't think
你那时也不会想要报道出去
you're planning to write it then either.
我有没有告诉过你
I ever tell you why I wanted
我为什么想要成为记者
to be a reporter in the first place?
是你关于红衣侠的报道
It was because of your article about the Streak.
你知道  那是我给闪电侠
You know, that was the first name
取的第一个名字
that I ever gave to the Flash.
那个时候  我还不知道他是巴里
Back then, I didn't even know that he was Barry.
当初  我只是一个在铁山监狱的问题儿童
And back then, I was just a troubled kid in Iron Heights,
但是你的文章
but your article,
让我相信了不可能
it made me believe in the impossible,
或许有一天我可以像你一样
that maybe someday I could be like you,
追踪报道  揭露真相
chasing stories, uncovering the truth.
你在我绝望的时候给我希望
You gave me hope when I had none...
我来这里工作的每一天你都这样
Just like you have every day I've worked here.
我不知道你是如何强迫自己去
I don't know how you're gonna bring yourself
写这篇文章
to write this article.
我只是知道
I just know
如果没写的话你是不会原谅自己的
you're never going to forgive yourself if you don't.
什么  我是怎么
What's--how did I?
艾伦
Allen.
看起来我们两个都恢复得不错啊
Looks like we're both back on our feet.
宝贝  我很高兴你感觉好些了
Babe, I'm glad you're feeling better.
-谢谢  -你看  我给你盛了一盘
- Thanks. - Look, I made you a plate.
太好吃了
Mmm,delicious.
我真的喜欢这个土豆泥
I'm all about these mashed potatoes.
我要再来一份这个豆子
I'm gonna need a second helping of these beans.
这个既是赞美  也是警告
That's both praise, and a warning.
这不对劲
This is wrong.
大家
Everyone.
我这里有自制千层面
I've got homemade lasagna.
巴里
Barry.
一点不吃很不礼貌
It's rude not to eat.
你不是爱瑞丝  这不是真的
You're not Iris. This isn't real.
我不会向你屈服的
I'm not gonna give in to you.
巴里  你误会我了
Barry, you misjudge me.
我来这只是为了跟好朋友一起吃晚餐的
I'm just here to enjoy supper with good friends
或许再给你一个礼物
and perhaps offer you a gift.
你还能给我什么
What could you possibly offer me?
一切
Everything.
闪电侠消失于危机中
巴里  你无法逃避你自己的思想
Barry, you can't run away from your own mind,
至少不会让你不痛不痒
at least not without considerable pain.
说到头  你总是试图
Then again, you're always trying
逃避问题  不是吗
to run away from your problems, aren't you?
你有一张报纸
You've literally had a newspaper
提醒你的死亡
warning of your demise.
你却对改变命运无动于衷
You've done nothing to change your fate.
就好像你想让爱瑞丝成为寡妇一样
It's almost like you want to make Iris a widow.
闭嘴
Shut up!
这不是真的
This isn't real.
这些死亡是真的
These deaths were real.
巴里·艾伦
他们都不必死的
None of them had to die.
加入我  你也不必死去
Join me, and you'll never have to.
诺拉
Nora.
求你了  让我抱抱她  我知道这不是真的
Please, let me hold her. I know it's not real, I just--
求你了  我只是想假装
please, I just wanna pretend for--
求你了  一秒也好
please, just for a second--
我只是  求你了  我想抱抱我的孩子
I just--please, I wanna hold my baby.
这不是我决定的  巴里
That's not my choice, Barry.
你为什么要给我看这些
Why are you showing this to me?
我什么都没给你看
I'm not showing you anything.
这些都是来自于你自己
All of this is coming from you.
不  这不是  不  这不是
No, it's not. No, it's not.
不  不  这不是
No... No, it's not.
往内心深处看  巴里·艾伦
Look deep within, Barry Allen.
这是你的思想  你的预见
This is your mind, your visions,
你的疑惑
your doubt.
没有你  我们都会死
We all die without you.
你永远不要来烦我
You leave me alone forever.
你的城市会燃烧
Your city will burn.
她比所有人都快
She's even faster than ever.
负神速力太多了  甚至对我也是
The negative Speed Forces were too much, even for me,
而现在  巴里  所有人都死了
and now, Barry, everyone is dead.
事情没有必要发展成这样的  巴里
It doesn't have to be like this, Barry.
来  让我带你看看
Here, let me show you.
中城公民报
闪电侠活下来了
拯救世界于危机中
接受我的生命之血  你可以用它来达到
Accept my lifeblood, and you could use it to achieve
我从未达到的高度
so much more than I ever could.
成为你想都没想过的英雄
Become a hero beyond your wildest dreams.
击败死亡的能力
The power to strike down death,
永生
life eternal,
伟大的奇迹由你掌控
the grand miracle at your command.
拯救世界并活下来
Save the world and live.
拥有你想要的一切
Have all you want.
她好漂亮
She's so beautiful.
接受它  巴里
Embrace it, Barry.
实话实说吧
Just confess the truth.
你有疑惑吗
Do you have doubts?
是的
I do.
这个生活非常美好  巴里
It's a beautiful life, Barry.
你需要做的是选择它
All you have to do is choose it.
选择生活
Choose life.
巴里
Barry...
你必须集中你的力量
You must gather your strength.
专注  要没时间了
Focus. Time is running out.
我想你们会想看下这个
Thought you all would want to see this.
目击者听到了爆炸声
Witnesses heard the explosion
但没看到其他的
but didn't see much else.
这里至少有六个摄像头
There's gotta be at least half a dozen cameras
覆盖到这个区域  我...
covering this lot. I--
但是事发时没有一个摄像头
And not one of them caught anyone entering or exiting
捕捉到有人出入现场
the scene when this all went down.
就好像是幽灵干的
It's like a ghost did this.
所以你询问的那家伙被杀死了
So the guy you questioned was killed
就在你询问他的那个地方  还是同一天
in the same lot you questioned him on the same day.
是的  越来越糟了
Yeah. It gets worse.
这个从现场炸走了
This blew away from the scene.
我想把它交给警察  但我看到它是因为
I thought about turning it in to the cops, but I only saw it
有强大的紫外线能量从这个东西中发出
because there's some major UV energy coming off this thing.
你能看到
You can see that?
老大  这真的好像是
Boss, this really feels like a job
你丈夫朋友的工作
for your husband's friend.
没事  卡米拉知道巴里是闪电侠
Oh, no, Kamilla knows that Barry's the Flash.
真的吗
Seriously?
什么时候知道的
Since when?
去年夏天  西斯科是震波的时候
Last summer. Cisco used to be Vibe.
好吧  各位  我认为这个迷
Okay, look, guys, I think this mystery
比我们想象的要难解
goes a lot deeper than we thought.
也更危险
And it's a lot more dangerous.
所以如果你们想离开的话
So if you guys wanna walk away--
不可能
Not a chance.
我也是
That makes two of us.
老大  看来公民报小队有了新任务
Well, Boss, looks like Team Citizen has a new mission.
没事的  巴里  我在这
It's okay, Barry. I'm here.
很抱歉花了这么久才找到你
I'm sorry it took me so long to find you.
拉姆齐的感染比我们之前遇到过的
Ramsey's infection is stronger than anything
都要强大
we've ever faced,
而且还会越来越强大
and it's only getting stronger.
我想我知道为什么
I think I know why.
你感到了疑惑
You feel doubt.
是的
I do.
你之前也响应过我们
You've answered our call before.
总是如此面临险境
It's always been difficult.
什么变了
What's changed?
我活的更长了
I've lived more.
我结婚了
I've gotten married,
看到了未来  那里...
seen a future where
我有一个女儿  她是我和爱瑞丝最美好的结合
I'll have a daughter who's the best of me and Iris combined.
我的人生大部分被过去驱使  但...
Most of my life has been driven by my past, but--
但现在  我...
but now, I--
我终于感到在为自己而活
It finally feels like I'm living for myself.
我不想离开我的家人和朋友
I don't wanna leave my family or my friends.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
我知道这很自私
I know that's selfish.
很抱歉我让你失望了
I'm sorry I let you down.
巴里
Barry.
没人会对害怕和怀疑免疫
No person is immune to fear and doubt...
不管有多勇敢
No matter how brave...
是人都会如此  巴里
That's what makes you human, Barry.
但前进的勇气
But the courage to move forward,
甚至是在面对极端不利的情况时
even in the face of overwhelming odds,
这才使你成为英雄
that's what makes you a hero.
这才使你成为闪电侠
That's what makes you the Flash.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我需要这些
I needed to hear that.
别怪你自己
Don't blame yourself.
他的谎言
His lies...
太让人信服
They were so convincing.
那是因为他从不撒谎
That's because he never lied.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
所以拉姆齐才如此危险
That's what makes Ramsey so dangerous.
他操纵事实来传播疾病
He manipulates the truth to spread his disease.
什么  所以
What, so--
所以那部分关于他的细胞
so the part about his cells
能让我能从危机中拯救世界
allowing me to save the world from Crisis and...
并且幸存下来是真的
still survive is true?
是的
Yes.
但那条路不适合你
But that path's not for you.
为什么不
Why not?
巴里  你必须明白
Barry, you must understand--
你希望我在有办法自救时还丢下所有
That you want me to leave behind everyone I love
我爱的人离开吗
when there's a way to save me?
怎么了
What is it?
是巴里的睡眠监测器  情况不对
It's Barry's sleep monitor. This can't be right.
他的生命指数在激增
His vitals are spiking.
巴里  你的体温正在升高  你必须冷静
Barry, your fever is rising. You must calm down.
别告诉我该做什么
Stop telling me what to do!
他的体温高得要烧起来了
His temperature is burning up.
他为什么没有极速恢复
Why isn't he speed-healing?
我以前见过这么高的烧
I've seen this fever before.
他的身体正在被接管
He's being taken over
就是现在
right now.
他的体温在升高
His temperature is rising.
我们现在真的用得上冰冻超能力了
We could really use some cold powers right about now.
不  拉姆齐的感染对冰没有反应
No, Ramsey's infection doesn't respond to ice.
我们得用药物来治疗他
We need to treat him medicinally.
注射10毫升萘普生钠
Inserting 10ccs of naproxen sodium.
我承受的所有痛苦  所有折磨
All my pain, all my suffering,
都是因为你
it's been because of you
因为你宁愿让我当闪电侠
because you would rather I be the Flash
而不让我去做我自己
than have anything that I want!
巴里  拜托
Barry, please.
我不否认你一直肩负重任
I am not denying the burden that you've carried,
但神速力只是想在你选择的
but the Speed Force has only ever tried to
这条路上指引你
be a guide on this path that you've chosen.
是闪电球从天而降  击中了我
The lightning bolt shot down from the sky and struck me!
不是我选的
I didn't choose this!
是你决定要改变我的人生
You decided to change my life,
我家人的人生  我的整个未来
my family's life, my entire future.
这是强加于我的
This was done to me!
我们需要帮助
We need help.
冰霜
Frost.
Frost!
深呼吸  深呼吸
Just breathe. Breathe.
深呼吸
Just breathe.
你要明白  你所扮演的角色对保持
Please understand. The role you play is vital
-万物的平衡至关重要  -别说了
- to the balance of all things. - Oh, stop.
宇宙平衡危在旦夕
There are universal forces at stake.
必须有人去保护它
They must be protected.
那我们其他人呢
What about the rest of us?
她说得对
She's right.
宇宙平衡确实危在旦夕
There are universal forces at stake.
遗憾的是她没有把你的人生考虑在内
It's just a pity she doesn't consider your life among them.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
他要不惜一切代价控制你的身体
He wants to possess your form no matter the cost.
代价
Cost?
所有那些墓碑
All those headstones?
那些人都因为我跟你的关系而死
Those people are dead because of my connection to you.
我还要因为你受多少次折磨
How many times do I have to suffer for you?
什么时候才轮到你受折磨
When is it your turn to suffer?
你能感觉到痛苦吗
Do you even feel pain?
不能
No,
至少不是你知道的那种痛苦
at least not as you know it.
怎么可能  神速力不是人类
How could it? The Speed Force isn't human.
它不明白活着的意义
It doesn't know what it means to be alive,
拥有一个家庭  去爱
to have a family, to love.
它只会伪装
It only pretends.
拉姆齐的感染在扭曲你的心灵
Ramsey's infection is twisting your heart.
你必须与之抗争  巴里
You have to fight it. Barry.
这不是你的真实感受
These aren't your true feelings.
你又对真相了解多少
What do you know about the truth?
你的长相不是这样的
This isn't what you look like.
这里也不是我以前的卧室  这是个骗局
This isn't my old bedroom. It's a trick.
你在操纵我  让我服从你的想法
This is you manipulating me so I'll do what you want.
这不是真的  我在乎你
That's not true. I care about you.
它在乎的只是利用你
All it cares about is using you.
-巴里  你必须听我说  -不  我不听
- Barry, you must listen to me. - No, I don't!
你不是我妈妈
You're not my mom.
你是我埋葬她的原因
You're the reason I buried her.
监视者  斯旺  神速力
The Monitor, Thawne, the Speed Force,
你已经被别人利用了太久
for too long, others have used you.
掌控你自己的人生吧
Take command of your life!
永远
Forever.
不不不  对不起  我不得不这样做
No, no, no, no, no. I'm sorry, I have to.
这是活下去的唯一方法
It's the only way to survive.
我们时间不多了  他很快就会回来
We don't have much time until he returns.
巴里  看着我
Barry, look at me.
接受拉姆齐的血能从即将到来的危机中
Accepting Ramsey's blood would save your body
拯救你的身体  但无法拯救你的灵魂
from the coming Crisis but not your soul.
你会失去你最好的一面  你的快乐
You would lose the best of you: your joy,
你的激情  你的光芒
your passion, your light,
爱瑞丝爱的那部分
the part of you that Iris loves.
别听它的  它会说谎
Don't listen to it. It lies.
拜托  巴里
Come on! Barry!
只有你能战胜他  巴里
Only you can defeat this, Barry.
选择权在你手里
The choice is yours.
你打败了它
You beat it.
花了我些时间  但是  没错  我打败了它
Took me a while, but, yeah, I beat it.
爱瑞丝·韦斯特艾伦报道  2019年12月11日  周三
我的名字叫爱瑞丝·韦斯特艾伦
My name is Iris West-Allen
我曾遇到一个年轻人
and I once met a young man,
一个被我叫做红衣侠的超级英雄
a superhero who I called the Streak.
世人皆知他就是现今世上速度最快的人
The world has come to know him as the Fastest Man Alive,
红衣极速者  闪电侠
the Scarlet Speedster, the Flash.
但是无论你为他取了什么绰号
But no matter what title you choose for him,
他永远不变的是我们这个
he'll always be remembered as the protector
伟大的城市与其中市民的守护者
of our amazing city and its citizens,
作为我们所有人希望的灯塔
as a beacon of hope for us all,
作为那个一次又一次
and as the man who sacrificed himself
牺牲自己保全我们生活的人
again and again so we could live.
今天我们对他说再见  不是因为他被夺走
Today we say good-bye to him, not because he was taken
而是因为他自愿做出牺牲
but because he gave himself willingly.
最终  这让他配得上
And in the end, that's what makes him deserving
所有头衔里最好的那个
of the greatest title of all...
英雄
Hero.
马尔·诺武
Mar Novu.
你跑啊跑啊穿过了无限的地球
You ran and ran across infinite Earths,
而现在你已无处可逃
and now you've nowhere left to run.
就像是
It was like
重回监狱  只是被监禁在我自己的大脑里
being back in prison only locked up in my own mind.
我感觉到的所有的恐惧
All the terror I felt,
我看到的所有的坏事
the horrible things I saw,
它们都在那里
they were all there
一直深埋在我的脑海里等着出来
buried deep inside me just waiting to come out the whole time.
费了很大劲才获胜
Took a lot to win.
所有让人生有价值的东西
Everything that makes life worth living.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
这里面也有你的功劳啊
You deserve some of the credit.
可不是谁都能打败一个有意识的感染
It takes something special to beat a sentient infection
甚至连极速恢复都搞不定
that not even speed-healing can cure.
无论如何  这还没结束  我们回去继续工作
Well, it's not over yet, so let's get back to work.
等等  你什么意思  你在干什么
Whoa, whoa, what do you mean? What are you doing?
就去歇着吧
Just get some rest.
爱瑞丝马上就到
Iris is gonna be here any minute.
危机还有不到36个小时就要到了
Crisis will be here in less than 36 hours.
我们要去找拉姆齐  阻止他
We have to find Ramsey, stop him,
确保还有个能拯救的世界
make sure there's still a world left to save.
他就这么走了
And away he goes.
你想谈谈发生了什么吗
You wanna talk about what happened?
我已经跟小凯谈过了
I already talked about it with Caity.
好  她怎么说的
Okay. What'd she say?
随着危机的临近  我们决定最好是
With Crisis approaching, we decided it would be best
让她来应付医疗急救
if she handles the medical emergencies.
我会退居二线
I'll take a back seat.
对此你同意吗
Are you okay with that?
这是对这个团队最好的
It's what's best for the team.
我尽我最快赶到了
Hey, I got here as fast as I could.
-你还好吗  -我很好
- How are you? - Oh, I'm fine.
真的  我很好
Really, I'm okay.
你的丈夫被感染了
Your husband had an infection...
这让他的大脑有些混乱  但被我们解决了
It messed with his brain quite a bit, but we handled it.
好的  安全起见
Okay, well, just to be safe,
我今晚余下的时间都不会离开你
I am not leaving you again for the rest of the night.
你在忙些什么
What you working on?
只是做些诊断
Just running some diagnostics,
一点保养
little maintenance.
你为什么不让西斯科来
Why don't you ask Cisco?
我们可以回家  一起待会儿
We could go home, spend some time together.
你为什么问这么多问题
Why are you asking so many questions?
我不知道  有时候
I don't know. You know, sometimes
我的记者思维有着
the reporter brain in me has a
它自己的意识
mind of its own.
我会让你继续工作
I will... let you get back to work.
朋友们
Hey, guys.
那不是巴里
That's not Barry.
小心点
Careful.
巴里
Barry.
欢迎  我的血亲们
Welcome, my blood brother.
我是这个世界的救赎
I am the world's salvation
来把它从所有的痛苦中拯救出来
come to save it from all that ails it.
很快  整个世界将会见识到
Soon, the entire world will embrace
血怒
Bloodwork!